Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Time-Life Broadcast, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  Issue: Severance pay - sale of business. (Award only).
- Times Wire and Cable Co. vs. UAW, Local 376, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 71)
- Torrington Co. vs. UAW, Local 1645, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; discipline - unsatisfactory work. (Award only).
- Townsend Co. vs. USA, Local 1164, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  Issue: Overtime - rates of pay; schedules of work - change of schedule. (Award only).
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Ravan, Gary L.; vs. TWUA Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association Local 550; vs. ALPA; vs. Gloria Bernard; vs. IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  Issue: Vacations - computation; sick leave and sick pay; transfers - disciplinary transfers; reinstatement; schedules of work - change of schedule; seniority - vacancies; discipline - discharge; improper job attitude; absences - excessive; working conditi
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. J.J. Thompson; TWU Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association Local 550, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; improper personal conduct - offensive language; past practice; fringe benefits; discipline - discharge; sick leave and sick pay; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - drinking prior to reporting; schedules of work - double
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs TWU Local 551; vs. Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association; vs. Don G. Nordyke; vs. Independent Federation of Flight Attendants, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  Issue: Schedules of work - rest breaks; evidence - sufficiency; back pay awards - compliance; arbitration procedure - appeal and review of award; discipline - discharge; absences - proof of illness; discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct. (Awa
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Independent Federation of Flight Attendants; vs. IAM Transport District Lodge No. 142, 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  Issue: Schedules of work - time off schedules; arbitrability - prior settlement; arbitrability - merit of claim. (Award Only.)
- Tremont Dodge Corp. vs UAW Local 259, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; improper personal conduct - toward supervisor. (Award Only.)
- Triangle Publications, Inc. (WNHC-TV) vs NABET; Triangle Publications, Gravure Division vs Philadelphia Newspaper Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union of North America, Local 16; Triangle Publications, Inc. vs Newspaper Guild of New York, 1961-1972 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit; schedules of work - shift scheduling; insurance - beneficiaries. (Award Only.)
- Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority vs. Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association, Inc., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  Issue: Vacancies - labor pool employees. (Award only).
- Tru-matic Machine and Tool Co., Inc. vs. USA, Local 5779, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  Issue: Demotions - seniority. (Award only).
- Tung-Sol Electric, Inc. vs. IBEW, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 82)
- Twentieth Century Vault Co. vs. Warehouse Employees, Local 169, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 83)
- Two Guys-Vornado, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks, Local 1357, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 84)
- United Air Lines, Inc. vs. IAM, District 141, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs past practice; Physical disability. (Award only).
- United Farmers of New England, Inc. vs. Milk Wagon Drivers and Creamery Workers Union, Local 380, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  Issue: Arbitrability - authority of arbitrator; transfers - transfers of work and machines. (Award only).
- United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Teachers' Representative Union, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  Issue: Holidays and holiday pay - undesignated holiday. (Award only).
- United Parcel Service vs. IBT Local 111, Local 30, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  Issue: Seniority; Discipline - discharge; discipline - negligence and carelessness. B, EX, RC, AN, SD, and photographs.
- United Press Association vs. American Newspaper Guild, Local 222; vs. Commercial Telegraphers' Union, United Press System 47, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  Issue: Reduction in force - seniority; absences - discipline. (Award Only.)
- United Press International vs. Commercial Telegraphers' Union, United Press System 47; vs. American Newspaper Guild, Wire Service Guild, Local 222, 1960- 1971 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  Issue: Contract modification - wage adjustments; insubordination - discipline; discipline - suspension; contract modification - interest arbitration. (Award Only.)
- United States Immigration and Naturalization Service vs AFGE Local 1917, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  Withdrawn. Issue: Safety - meetings - frequency. RC, AN, B, EX, TR.
- United States Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC); vs. American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; absences - proof of illness; suspension, insubordination; discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; discipline - suspension - violation of plant rules; discipline - suspension - improper personal conduct - disruptive in
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, Branch 36; vs. APWU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  Issue: Safety - past practice; arbitrability - grievance procedure, failure to follow; discipline - discharge; discipline - suspension; theft - employee liability for robbery; suspensions - pending court action; back pay awards - reinstatement; discipline
- United States Postal Service vs APWU; vs. NALC, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; improper personal conduct - toward supervisor; discipline - substandard performance; applications for employment - falsification; absences - proof of illness; termination of employment - probationary employee; drugs - sale a
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC; vs. APWU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Issue: Termination of employment - following physical disability, mental illness; discipline - probation; discipline - discharge - fights and altercations.
- United States Postal Service vs APWU; vs NALC, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 1a)
  Issue: Quits - withdrawal of resignation; discipline - discharge; union representatives and business - insubordination; grievance and grievance procedure - prior settlement; sick leave and sick pay - moonlighting; discipline - discharge; absences - unauth
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC; vs. APWU, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 1b)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; termination of employment - following illness or physical disability; reinstatement - following mental illness; discipline - discharge - drugs - sale and use; physical disability - termination of employment following; di
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC; vs. LIUNA, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Issue: Reinstatement - following mental illness; discipline - discharge - fights and altercations; discipline - discharge - insubordination - threats. (Award Only)
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA; vs. APWU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination; termination of employment - absences - reasons; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; falsification - absence reports; termination of employment - following illness or physical disability; disciplin
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. LIUNA, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; tardiness; suspension - insubordination - refusal of work assignment. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - reinstatement - mental illness; discipline - discharge - theft; discipline - discharge - incompetence and inefficiency. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft; discipline - discharge - absences; discipline - discharge - absences - falsification of report; discipline - discharge - unauthorized use of company property. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC; vs. APWU, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude; absences; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive, incompetence and inefficiency; discipline - discharge - application for employment - falsification; drugs - use; suspension - pending court acti
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - suspension - pending court action; arbitrability - waiver; arbitrability - scope of issue; back pay awards - conditional; back pay awards - computation; back pay awards - interest; absences - unauthorized; absences, excessi
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft - pilfering, company property; discipline - discharge - unsatisfactory work - standards of production. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC; vs. LIUNA, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - strikes, slowdowns, and work stoppages; breach of no-strike clause; discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; discipline - discharge - insubordination; improper job attitude - sleeping on the job. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; absences - unauthorized; discipline - discharge - drug use; discipline - discharge - theft; discipline - discharge - absences - unauthorized; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; discipline - d
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; absences - unauthorized; discipline - discharge - drug use; discipline - discharge - theft; discipline - discharge - absences - unauthorized - absences, excessive; discipline - discharge - strikes, slow
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercations; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; tardiness; absences - reasons - false; absences - excessive; tardiness; discipline - discharge - alcoholism. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; absences - unauthorized; discipline - discharge - fights and altercations, verbal assaults; improper personal conduct - profanity; discipline - discharge - theft - misappropriation. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Issue: Termination of employment - incompetence and inefficiency; discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; quits - voluntary; grievance - arbitrability. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; discipline - discharge - theft; discipline - discharge - fights and altercations; timeliness - appeal to arbitration. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Issue: Termination of employment - mental illness. (Award only).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - conviction of crime. RC, B, EX, SD, AN. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive. RC,B,SD, EX, AN. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU; vs. NALC, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  Issue: Suspension pending court action; Discipline - discharge - drug use; absences - excessive.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Issue: Improper job conduct. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  Withdrawn. RC, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercations; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; discipline - discharge - alcoholism; insubordination. (Award Only.)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  Withdrawn. RC, B, SD, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercation. RC, B, AN, EX, SD. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercation. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  Issue: Termination of employment - physical disability. RC, B, AN, SD, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination, threats. RC, B, EX, AN. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  Issue: Improper job attitude - interference with production. RC, B, AN, EX, SD. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercation. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - unauthorized. RC, B, EX, AN. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - unauthorized, excessive. RC, B, EX, AN. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive. RC, B, EX, AN. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, unauthorized. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - application for employment - falsification. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft - misappropriation. RC, B, AN, EX, SD. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  Issue: Suspension - fights and altercation. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  Withdrawn. RC, B, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  Issue: Absences - falsification of reports. RC, B, EX, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification - rates of pay. RC, B, EX, AN, SD and photographs.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  Issue: Holidays - holiday pay; schedules of work. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - vacancies. RC, B, EX, SD, AN, Agreement.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  Issue: Suspension - conviction of crime. RC, B, EX, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  Issue: Schedules of work - holidays. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  Issue: Suspension - conviction of crime. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  Issue: Overtime - seniority. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification. RC, B, AN, EX, SD.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Issue: Theft. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Issue: Physical disability - assignment of job. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - disability - termination of employment. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct - abuse of property. RC, B, AN, EX, SD. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - excessive; improper job attitude. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, unauthorized. RC, B, AN, EX, SD. (No award).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  Issue: Compensation - damages - carelessness and negligence. RC, B, EX, SD.
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, tardiness as. RC, B, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  Issue: Overtime - seniority - assignment of jobs. (Award only).
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  Issue: Vacations - eligibility. RC, B, AN, SD.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercations. RC, B, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive. RC, B, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  Issue: Promotion - seniority. RC, B, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  Issue: Promotions - testing. RC, B, EX, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - sick leave - chronic illness.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  Issue: Transfers - promotions - qualifications. RC, B, EX, SD, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - conviction of crime; improper personal conduct - gambling. RC, B, SD, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  Issue: Suspension - theft. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive. RC, B, EX, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - improper job attitude.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - conviction of crime. RC, B, EX, AN.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - alcoholism; negligence and carelessness. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- United States Postal Service vs. LIUNA, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - tardiness; absences - excessive. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  Issue: Discharge - physical disability - absences, excessive. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU (Box 20, Folder 40)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - drugs, possession. AN, RC, B, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. APWU, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  Issue: Physical disability - reinstatement following; vacancies - seniority. RC, B, SD, AN, LD, EX.
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- United States Postal Service vs. NALC, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- United States Steel Corp. vs. USA Local 1066; vs. USA Local 4889; vs. USA Local 5092; vs. USA Local 1924, 1954-1962 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - creation of new classification; assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification; vacations - schedules; promotion - seniority; assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work. (Award Only.)
- United States Steel Corp. vs USA Local 1924; vs. USA Local 1397; vs. USA Local 4889; vs. USA Local 1397, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - change in work assignments - promotion; safety - protective clothing; safety - specific hazards; rates of pay - time not worked; assignment of jobs - temporary assignment of safety; classification of jobs - new position. (A
- United States Steel Corp. vs. USA Local 4889; vs. USA Local 1489; vs. USA Local 1397, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - discontinuance of classification; assignment of jobs - seniority - rates of pay; apprentices - promotions. (Award Only.)
- United States Steel Corp. vs. USA Local 1489; vs. USA Local 1397; vs. USA Local 1733; vs. USA Local 2210; vs. USA Local 1489, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification; assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside unit; strikes, slowdowns - suspension; layoff - procedure; assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside classification.
- United States Steel Corp vs. USA Local 1013; vs. USA Local 1397; vs. USA Local 1445 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside classification; classification of jobs - promotion. (Award Only.)
- United States Veterans Administration vs. AFGE, Local 1151 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - application of employment - falsification. RC, B, AN, EX.
- United States Veterans Administration vs. AFGE, Local 1151 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- United Telephone Co. of New Jersey vs. Telephone Worker of New Jersey, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  Issue: Schedules of work holidays work week; Work week - holidays. (Award only).
- Varig Brasilian Airlines vs. IAM, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude - interference with production. (Award only).
- Vellumoid Co. vs. USA, Local 5683, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - unauthorized absence. (Award only).
- Vickers, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 1335, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Vickers, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 1335, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  Issue: Termination of employment - quits - self-induced. (Award only).
- WBRE Radio, Inc. vs. NABET, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  Issue: Termination of employment - testing - promotions - unsatisfactory work. (Award only).